Fox Family and G. Fox & Co. Collection 0012.002.008b
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
Fox Family and G. Fox & Co.
1847-1960
0012.002.008b
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
10.0 Cubic feet 15 Boxes 1 Oversized Box 1 Scrapbook Artifacts
Fox Family Tree
Fox Auerbach family tree
See also family trees prepared by Rena Koopman 3/2007 filed under Fox Auerbach Family/Koopman Family/family tree
Gerson Fox (1811-80) = Hannah Bamberger (d. 1875) Isaac Louis and Mary / \ \ \ / / \ Moses (1850-1938) = 1. Sophie (d. 1883) Isaac Leopold Emma Jacob L. (1856-1936) Levi Isaac (d. 1862) 2. Theresa Stern (1865-1932) = Sadie Neweity = ___ Plaut = Miriam Stern (d. 1910) / \ \ \ \ / Beatrice Fox Auerbach Fannie Fox Auerbach Hattie = ___Bass Hortense Blanche Lewis (1904-77)
Ferdinand Stern = Fannie Kurtz / Theresa Miriam Sancha Moses Sarah Ida Maud Bessie Flora Frederick Benjamin Lena = Moses Fox = Jacob L. Fox = Morris Marks Sr. = ___Michael = ___Wolfe = ___Silluvan =___Schoenfield =___Newman / / / Beatrice, Lewis Morris Jr. Fannie
G. Fox & Co. Store
Founded by Gerson Fox in 1847 as a "fancy goods" store, the department store chain eventually known as G. Fox & Co. became the largest family-owned department store in the country and the preeminent retail establishment in Hartford. According to some sources, Gerson and his brother Isaac opened a store in Hartford as early as 1840. Isaac left for New York a few years later.
Gerson's son Moses joined the store in 1863 when he was 13. In 1880, the property on Main Street that would eventually house the main store was purchased, and a four-story building was erected there. This store burnt down in 1917, but after the fire, an eleven-story building was built on the site. The eleven-story store reflected the major changes in retail shopping that were occurring in America.
Women of the early 20th century acquired new-found leisure time provided by labor-saving inventions. Unlike the old-fashioned store that one did not enter without a purpose, where merchandise was hidden in cupboards until the clerk brought it out, this new store offered many new services especially for these women who now shopped as much for entertainment as for the accomplishment of an errand.
After the death of Moses in 1938, his daughter Beatrice Fox Auerbach, who had joined the store in 1927 at the death of her husband, took over its leadership. She expanded both the store and its offerings to the shopper. The hair salon became almost spa-like, women could dine in the roof garden, and various departments offered various types of education to help women understand their new appliances or design a tasteful interior.
Mrs. Auerbach also set new standards for service to customers. Many local legends grew about instances where the company went far beyond the custom to supply distant shoppers with spools of thread or to replace the upholstery on five-year-old chairs. The working climate was also an improvement over that found in other stores. Although the pay was said to be low, job security was high and the store worked hard to make every employee feel special.
In 1965, G. Fox & Co. was sold to the May Company. In 1992, the May Co., which also owned the much larger and regionally better known Filene's, retired the G. Fox name after 117 years of service and converted those stores to Filene's.
Fox Family
Much has been written on the Fox and Auerbach families in Morris Silverman's book, so a detailed biographical sketch will not be given here. The following outline will put the collection in context.
In 1847, Gerson Fox, an immigrant from Germany, founded the dry goods store that eventually became G. Fox and Company. Various members of his family and his relatives' families worked for the company, building it from a small shop to a large department store chain well-known throughout Connecticut for its service.
Leadership in the store passed to Gerson's son, Moses Fox, in 1880. His first wife, Sophie Korn died in 1883, and their daughter Sophie died at the age of 11. Moses married Theresa Stern, daughter of a retailer in Newburgh, N.Y., and they had two daughters, H. Beatrice and Fannie. [Jacob L. Fox, a first cousin of Moses, married Miriam Stern, the sister of Theresa.]
In 1911, Beatrice (1887-1968) married George S. Auerbach, who operated his own family's store, Auerbach's, in Salt Lake City. After fire destroyed the G. Fox & Co. building in 1917, Beatrice and her husband returned to Hartford to help with the construction of a new store. George Auerbach became treasurer of G. Fox but died prematurely in 1927. Beatrice went to work at the store following his death. She stayed on and became president in 1938 at the death of Moses Fox.
Beatrice became a legend in Hartford retailing. She was intimately involved with the operation of her store, tirelessly greeting customers, talking daily with the clerks, inspecting every corner of the building. Her aim was to achieve a new level of excellence in providing model service. Under her direction, G. Fox & Co. became the largest family-owned retail operation in the country. In 1965, she sold the chain to the May Co.
Beatrice was also tireless in her financial support of the community, endowing educational programs and scholarships at local colleges, subsidizing cultural programs such as the Wadsworth Atheneum and Hartford Symphony, and contributing to many major social service agencies such as hospitals, the Hebrew Home, and the Federation. The Beatrice Fox Auerbach Foundation, which she founded, continues her work in the community. In recognition of her interest and service, she was elected to seats on many local boards.
Beatrice also saw the usefulness of women's organizations in improving the community. She established the Service Bureau for Women's Organizations to provide training and programming for the leaders of these organizations. A world traveler, Beatrice sent back reports on world problems and economic conditions to the community through the Service Bureau.
The history of this family provides research opportunities in several areas, including the study of German Jewish immigrants and the patterns of their business and social circles, the role of women's groups in shaping the community and the view that members had of their work, American retailing history, private philanthropy and its role in shaping a community, and the dynamics of the acceptance of an independent Jewish woman into the top ranks of a very traditional early 20th century male-dominated community.
Auerbach, Beatrice Fox, Business, Civic Leader, Philanthropist, 07/07/1887 - 11/29/1968, Hartford, CT; Fox, Gerson, Retailer, Dry Goods, (Fox, Gershon Fuchs), 12/15/1811 - 08/22/1880, Bekunstadt, Germany; Fox, Jacob, Retailer, Vice-president, G. Fox & Co., 03/26/1856 - 02/23/1936, Ellsworth, ME; Fox, Lewis, Law, 1904 - 1977, Hartford, CT; Fox, Louis, Business, b.1856, Ellsworth, ME; Fox, Miriam Stern; Fox, Moses, Retailer, President, G. Fox & Co., 12/26/1850 - 01/13/1938, Hartford, CT; Fox, Theresa Stern, 02.23/1865 - 01/28/1932, Newburgh, NY; Beatrice Fox Auerbach Foundation; Congregation Beth Israel; G. Fox & Co.; Hartford Board of Education
- Series I: Louis and Miriam Fox
  - Louis Fox/Financial Records/Business Ledger 1848-49 and Cash Journal 1857-66, 1848-1856
  - Louis Fox/Financial Records/Home Journal 1861-66, 1861-1866
  - Miriam Stern Fox/Birthday and Anniversary Datebook, 1903
  - Miriam Stern Fox/Obituaries and Condolences, undated
- Series II: Scrapbooks
  - Oversized scrapbook, 1922-1937, 1850-1996
- Series III: Fox Family Artifacts
  - Ceremonial hood and gown worn by Lewis Fox at reception of honorary doctoral degree, undated
  - Large felt banner labeled "Princeton 1926"
  - Black and orange knit tie (probably Princeton related), undated
  - Four pennants labeled: Camp Greylock, Clio, Camp Wigwam, and Princeton, undated
  - 2 American flags, undated
  - Felt armband with initials "NWS" (probably Noah Webster School), undated
  - Cap with initials "Asylum Hill Cadets", undated
  - Sewing kit of Miriam Stern Fox, undated
  - Bible, undated
  - Brass and enamel breast plate for Torah scroll, undated
  - Brass plates from award plaques, undated
  - Leather 3-ring binder, undated
  - Hartford Public High School Yearbook, 1977
  - Music book of Miriam Stern Fox, undated
  - G. Fox paper and plastic bags, undated
  - Advertisements, undated
- Series IV: Fox Family
  - Auerbach Family, undated
  - Auerbach, Fannie Fox - Biographical, undated
  - Auerbach, Fannie Fox - Obituaries, undated
  - Auerbach, H. Beatrice Fox - Awards and Honors, undated
  - Auerbach, H. Beatrice Fox - Biographical, undated
  - Auerbach, H. Beatrice Fox -- Charitable Activities - Beatrice Fox Auerbach Foundation, undated
  - Auerbach, H. Beatrice Fox -- Civic Activities -- Service Bureau for Women's Organizations, undated
  - Auerbach, H. Beatrice Fox -- Correspondence, undated
  - Auerbach, H. Beatrice Fox -- Correspondence/Hebrew Sheltering and Immigrant Aid Society, 1930s, undated
  - Auerbach, H. Beatrice Fox -- Home -- 1040 Prospect Avenue, Hartford, undated
  - Auerbach, H. Beatrice Fox -- Miscellaneous, undated
  - Auerbach, H. Beatrice Fox -- Obituaries, undated
  - Auerbach, Josephine and Joseph Siegel/wedding souvenir, 1913, undated
  - Fox, Gerson -- Obituaries, undated
  - Fox, Moses -- Correspondence, undated
  - Fox, Moses -- Miscellaneous, undated
  - Fox, Moses -- Travel, undated
  - Fox, Theresa Stern - Birthday Party Guest Book, 1927
  - Fox, Theresa Stern - Civic Activities - Program from Conference on the Cause and Cure of War, 1925, undated
  - Koopman Family/family tree prepared by Rena Koopman, 3/2007, undated
  - Koopman Family – Miscellaneous, undated
  - Koopman, Georgette/Sunday School notes from Beth Israel, 1927-1928, undated
  - Schiro Family - Miscellaneous, undated
  - Stern, Ferdinand – Obituaries, undated
  - Surname Project, undated
- Photo Series I: Fox Family Photographs
  - Auerbach family groups; Fannie Fox-Bass; Hattie Fox This box contains both original photos and many reproductions mounted on foam board., undated
  - Auerbach, Fannie Fox, undated
  - Auerbach, George (husband of Beatrice), undated
  - Auerbach, George and H. Beatrice -- Family Wedding Photos, 1911
  - Auerbach, Georgette and Dorothy, undated
  - Auerbach, H. Beatrice Fox -- Family Grouping (Susan Schiro Wedding, 1967), undated
  - Bass, Hattie Fox (daughter of Leopold Fox), undated
  - Four Generations: Fannie, Theresa, Beatrice & Georgette, undated
- Photo Series II: Fox Family Photographs
  - Beatrice Fox Auerbach in youth, undated
  - Auerbach, H. Beatrice Fox (in youth), undated
  - Auerbach, H. Beatrice Fox (in youth), undated
- Photo Series III: Fox Family Photographs
  - Beatrice Fox Auerbach as adult. Includes formal portraits, events related to her career, photo of her at her desk, photos with Eleanor Roosevelt., undated
  - Auerbach, H. Beatrice Fox (adult), undated
  - Auerbach, H. Beatrice Fox/wedding photo with George Auerbach, undated
  - Auerbach, H. Beatrice Fox /four generation photo with Beatrice’s mother, grandmother, and daughter Georgette as a baby, undated
  - Lewis Fox as a child, undated
  - Lewis Fox as an adult, undated
  - Lewis Fox/Groups/family, undated
  - Lewis Fox/Group photos/Hartford Public High School in OVERSIZE box, undated
- Photo Series IV: Fox Family Photographs
  - Fox, Gerson, Hannah, Isaac, Jacob, Miriam Stern, and Louis Unframed photos, undated
  - Fox, Gerson and Hannah, undated
  - Fox, Gerson and Hannah (Family Groupings), undated
  - Fox, Isaac (son of Gerson), undated
  - Fox, Jacob L., undated
  - Fox, Jacob L. and Lewis, undated
  - Fox, Jacob L. and Miriam Stern, undated
  - Fox, Jacob L. and Miriam - Home at 74 Oxford Street, Hartford, undated
  - Fox, Leopold and Sadie (son of Gerson), undated
  - Fox, Lewis (Youth), undated
  - Fox, Lewis (Youth), circa 1915
  - Fox, Lewis (Youth)/as a child in sailor suit, OVERSIZE drawer, undated
  - Fox, Lewis (Adult), undated
  - Fox, Lewis - Camp Greylock, 1917
  - Fox, Lewis - Camp Greylock, 1918
  - Fox, Lewis - Chapel and Chaplaincy at Hartford Hospital, undated
  - Fox, Lewis - Friends from High School, undated
  - Fox, Lewis - Home at 750 Prospect Avenue, Hartford, undated
  - Fox, Miriam Stern, mother of Lewis Fox, miniature in case lined with blue velvet, undated
- Photo Series V: Fox Family Photographs
  - Louis, Mary, Miriam, Moses, undated
  - Fox, Louis and Mary (brother of Gerson, father of Jacob L.), undated
  - Fox, Miriam Stern, undated
  - Fox, Moses (son of Gerson), undated
  - Fox, Moses - Family Groupings, undated
- Photo Series VI: Fox Family Photographs
  - Sophie, Theresa, Anna, Julia, Morris, Sancha, Jacob Newman, Flora, Ferdinand, Fannie, Moses Stern, undated
  - Fox, Sophie Korn and her mother (1st wife of Moses Fox), undated
  - Fox, Sophie (with H. Beatrice Fox) (Sophie was daughter of Sophie Korn Fox), undated
  - Fox, Theresa Stern (wife of Moses), undated
  - Fulling, Anna M., undated
  - Keysor or Keyser, Julia, undated
  - Marks, Morris, Jr. (some with Lewis Fox), undated
  - Marks, Sancha Stern (sister of Miriam and Theresa, wife and mother of Morris Sr. and Jr.), undated
  - Miscellaneous, undated
  - Newman, Jacob L. and Flora Stern, undated
  - Stern, Ferdinand and Fannie, undated
  - Stern, Moses (brother of Theresa and Miriam), undated
- Photo Series VII: Fox Family Photographs (oversized, unframed):
  - Fannie Fox, 1909, undated
  - Unidentified women's group with H. Beatrice Fox, undated
  - Auerbach, George and Beatrice Fox, wedding picture, filed with OVERSIZE people photos, undated
  - Beacon Street School class photo, 1903, with H. Beatrice Fox
  - H. Beatrice Fox Auerbach with Eleanor Roosevelt and Lady Reading, undated
  - Stern Family gathering for 50th Anniversary of Ferdinand and Fannie Stern, 1908, undated
  - Emma Fox Plaut, Moses Fox, H. Beatrice Fox Auerbach, Georgette Auerbach, undated
  - Benjamin-Deane School class photo, 1906, with H. Beatrice Fox
  - Carol Marks (Bobrow?), daughter of Morris Marks Sr. and Sancha Stern Marks - wedding photo, No date, undated
  - Sancha Stern Marks with son Morris Jr., undated
  - Flora Stern Newman, no date (1920s), undated
  - Fox monument, Beth Israel Cemetery, undated
  - Jacob L. Fox on board a ship to Panama, 1914
  - Hartford Businessmen's Association Annual Banquet, 1915, with Jacob L. Fox
  - Unidentified male, undated
  - Unidentified male, undated
  - Fannie Kurtz Stern, Theresa Stern Fox, H. Beatrice Fox Auerbach, Georgette Auerbach, undated
  - Moses Fox, Grossman print, 1936
  - Gerson and Hannah Fox with their children Ike (Isaac), Emma, Leopold, Moses, undated
  - Wedding photo: Theresa Stern Fox, 1911
  - Wedding photo: Moses Fox, 1911
  - Wedding photo: Moses, Theresa, Fannie, H. Beatrice Fox, and George Auerbach, 1911, 3 copies Georgette Auerbach with dog, 1920, undated
  - H. Beatrice Fox Auerbach with daughters Georgette and Dorothy, 1928, undated
  - H. Beatrice Fox Auerbach with daughters Georgette and Dorothy, 1924, undated
  - H. Beatrice Fox Auerbach, no date (1930s), undated
  - H. Beatrice Fox Auerbach, 1942
  - H. Beatrice Fox Auerbach, 1924
  - Theresa Stern Fox in Spain, 1911
  - Theresa Stern Fox, 5 views, one with sister Sancha, 1899, undated
  - Princeton Debating Team with Lewis Fox, no date 2 poses, undated
  - Lewis Fox receiving honorary degree from Univ. of Hartford, 1967, undated
  - Lewis Fox, 1938
  - Lewis Fox, no date (about 8-10 years of age), undated
  - Lewis Fox, no date (about 40-45 years of age) 2 copies, undated
  - Lewis Fox and Jacob L. Fox, ca 1930-34 3 poses
  - Lewis Fox and Jacob L. Fox, 1911, undated
  - Lewis Fox, age 29 2 copies, undated
  - Lewis Fox, age 29 2 copies, undated
  - Jacob L. Fox, Miriam Stern Fox, Lewis Fox, undated
- Photo Series VIII: Fox Family Photographs Box 1a)
  - Lewis Fox, age 6 months, undated
  - Lewis Fox in Hartford Public High School group photo, undated
  - Lewis Fox, about age 3 or 4, undated
  - Lewis Fox, ca 1915, undated
  - Anna Fulling, undated
  - Three boys, unidentified [an unframed duplicate photo identifies them as "Bennie, Herbert, and Oscar, nephews of Moe"], undated
  - Fannie and Ferdinand Stern, undated
  - Aaron Stern, undated
  - Hannah Stern, undated
  - Noah Webster School Graduation class photograph, 1918, incl. Lewis Fox
  - Noah Webster School Graduation Certificate for Lewis Fox, 1918
  - Sketch of 750 Prospect Avenue, home of Lewis Fox, undated
  - Set of photos of Lewis Fox at age 6 months with Morris Marks, Jr., and an unidentified child, undated
- Photo Series IX: Fox Family Photographs (Box 2a)
  - Lewis Fox, about age 20, with Anna Fulling, undated
  - Lewis Fox, about age 7 or 8, undated
  - Lewis Fox as a young attorney in his office, undated
  - Louis and Mary Fox, undated
  - Lewis Fox, about age 7, with Morris Marks, Jr., undated
  - Lewis Fox, about age 18, with Jacob L. Fox and Morris Marks, Sr., undated
  - Miriam Stern Fox, undated
  - Lewis Fox, about age 2 or 3, undated
  - Lewis Fox and Jacob L. Fox, 1922
  - Lewis Fox, Jacob L. Fox, and Moses Fox, 1926
  - Hartford Public High School - Board of the Owlet newspaper, 1922, incl. Lewis Fox, undated
  - Hartford Public High School - students, no date, incl. Lewis Fox, undated
  - Hartford Public High School - students, no date, incl. Lewis Fox, undated
  - Hartford Public High School - Board of the Chronicle magazine, no date, incl. Lewis Fox, undated
  - Hartford Public High School - Debating Club, 1922, incl. Lewis Fox
  - Fannie Kurtz Stern, Theresa Stern Fox, Beatrice Fox Auerbach, and Georgette Auerbach, undated
  - Hannah Fox, wife of Gerson Fox, undated
  - Framed Photographs and Paintings formerly on Display in Reading Room of old office in JCC, undated
  - Jacob L. Fox, Miriam Fox, and Lewis Fox, undated
  - Four oil portraits of boys, perhaps from the Stern Family, undated
  - Gerson Fox, undated
  - Fannie Kurtz Stern, undated
  - Theresa Stern Fox, undated
  - H. Beatrice Fox as a girl, undated
  - Fannie Fox as a young woman, undated
  - Moses Fox, undated
  - Ferdinand Stern, undated
  - Stern or Fox Family, undated
- Series I: G. Fox & Co. Store Collection
  - Advertising, undated
  - Building Re-use, 1992 to Present
  - Closing, 1992, undated
  - Correspondence/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Correspondence/To Morris A. Fierberg, 1936-1963
  - Employee and Shopper Reminiscences, undated
  - Employee Newsletter, undated
  - Gift Certificate, 1980s, undated
  - History/Carsky, Mary L. and Donnellan, John F. "G. Fox: Grand Emporium of the 20th Century", undated
  - History/"A Century in Connecticut" Advertising Series, undated
  - History/Hendrickson, Robert "The Grand Emporiums", undated
  - History/Marks, Lita "A History of G. Fox and Company as an Urban Institution", undated
  - History/Miscellaneous, undated
  - May Company Ownership, 1965-1992
  - Miscellaneous, undated
  - Moses Fox Club, undated
  - Research paper/Marks, Lita/A History of G. Fox and Company as an Urban Institution, 1982, undated
- Series I: Lewis Fox Collection
  - A-Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships, undated
  - Awards and Honors/Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce, undated
  - Awards and Honors/Charter Oak Leadership Medal, 1963
  - Awards and Honors/Hartford Board of Education, - naming of Lewis Fox Middle School, 1971, undated
  - Awards and Honors/Hartford Public High School - naming of Lewis Fox Memorial Library, 1977, undated
  - Awards and Honors/Lewis Fox Memorial Lecture Series, undated
  - Awards and Honors/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Awards and Honors/University of Hartford Honorary Degree, 1967, undated
  - Biographical, undated
  - Charitable Activities/Anna M. Fulling Chaplaincy Endowment, 1956, undated
  - Charitable Activities/Hartford Hospital Interfaith Chapel Donation, 1964, undated
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Award given to Lewis Fox by Scholars, undated
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Anniversaries, undated
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Correspondence/Saltzman, Seymour, undated
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Death of Lewis Fox and continuation of Foundation, 1976-1979, undated
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/List of Scholars, undated
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/News Clippings Regarding Awards and Scholars, undated
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Reminiscences by Scholars, undated
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Scholars' Activities/, undated
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Summary of Information, 1963
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Summary of Information, 1964
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Summary of Information, 1965
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Summary of Information, 1966
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Summary of Information, 1967
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Summary of Information, 1968
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Summary of Information, 1969
- Series II: Lewis Fox Collection
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships – Civic Activities/Beth Israel, undated
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Summary of Information, 1971
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Summary of Information, 1972
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Summary of Information, 1972
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Summary of Information, 1974
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Summary of Information, 1975
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Speeches and Lectures, undated
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Trust Agreement and By-laws, undated
  - Charitable Activities/Jacob L. Fox Scholarships/Trustees, undated
  - Charitable Activities/Miriam Stern Fox Lecture at Beth Israel, undated
  - Civic Activities/Beth Israel High School Class - Lesson Files 1966-68, 1966-1968
  - Civic Activities/Beth Israel High School Class - Lesson Files 1968-70, 1968-1970
  - Civic Activities/Beth Israel High School Class - Lesson Files 1970-72, 1970-1972
  - Civic Activities/Beth Israel High School Class - Lesson Files 1972-74, 1972-1974
  - Civic Activities/Beth Israel High School Class - Lesson Files, 1974-76, 1974-1976
- Series III: Lewis Fox Collection
  - Civic Activities/Fellowship of Christian Athletes-Civic Activities/Hartford Board of Education, undated
  - Civic Activities/Fellowship of Christian Athletes, undated
  - Civic Activities/Greater Hartford Interracial Scholarship Committee, undated
  - Civic Activities/Hartford Board of Education, undated
  - Civic Activities/Hartford Board of Education - Bound Volume - 1937 Campaign, undated
  - Civic Activities/Hartford Board of Education - Bound Volume - 1941 Campaign, undated
  - Civic Activities/Hartford Board of Education - Bound Volume - 1945 Campaign, undated
  - Civic Activities/Hartford Board of Education - Bound Volume - 1949 Campaign, undated
  - Civic Activities/Hartford Board of Education - Bound Volume - 1955 Campaign, undated
- Series IV: Lewis Fox Collection
  - Civic Activities/Hartford Board of Education-Z, undated
  - Civic Activities/Hartford Board of Education - Bound Volume - 1961Campaign, undated
  - Civic Activities/Hartford Board of Education - 1961 Campaign (Folder), undated
  - Civic Activities/Hartford Board of Education - Bound Volume - 1965 Campaign, undated
  - Civic Activities/Hartford Board of Education - Bound Volume - 1969 Campaign, undated
  - Civic Activities/Hartford Board of Education - Bound Volume - 1973 Campaign, undated
  - Civic Activities/Hartford County YMCA, undated
  - Civic Activities/Salvation Army of Greater Hartford Advisory Board, undated